Oh, it's small.
あら、小さいな
Oh, can you take it off?
あら、脱いでくれるの?
Even if you sweat?
汗かいても?
Why don't you take off your clothes a little?
ちょっと脱ぎ脱ぎしないの?
Take your time.
じっくり
I didn't take it so carefully.
そんなじっくり取らなくて
difficult.
難しい
What should I do?
どうしよう
Because it's important.
大事なところだから
As usual.
普段通りで
fault.
あら
You ran away.
逃げたね
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
fault.
あら
Oh, you're taking a shower.
あら、シャワー受けてるね
That's a beautiful waist.
綺麗な腰ね
fault.
あら
hot?
熱い?
Take your time.
じっくり
difficult.
難しい
Where does it come from?
どこからあらうの?
tits.
おっぱい
tits?
おっぱい?
Right breast.
右おっぱい
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
warm?
温かい?
warm.
温かい
Hino-chan.
ひのちゃん
I want you to wash it too.
俺も洗ってほしいな
From where?
どこから?
tits.
おっぱい
Is it sweet?
甘いの?
Isn't it hot?
熱くない?
It's okay.
大丈夫だね
Just like this.
ちょっとこんな
cute.
かわいい
It's like this.
こんな感じ
こんな感じだね
i'm back.
戻ってきました
The temperature.
温度がね
Because it suits my face.
顔に合ってるから
nice.
いいね
It's a nice atmosphere.
いい雰囲気だね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
It's just breasts after all.
や っぱりおっぱいだよな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Is it warm?
温 かい?
warm.
温かい
That's amazing.
すごいね
You've gotten better at it.
上手になったね
Not good at it?
上手くない?
I've filled up the water, so let's go home together.
お湯を張ったから、一緒に帰ろう
The temperature is tough.
温度が大変だね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Oh, it's lukewarm.
お、ぬるい
Super lukewarm.
超ぬるい
cute.
かわいい
Which side?
どっち側?
scared.
怖い
Good at it.
上手い
Good.
上 手い
Not good at it?
上手くない?
Good at it.
上手い
Good.
上 手い
tasty
美味
Is it?
しい?
Yeah.
うん
Have you taken a breather?
一 息ついた?
A place where I can take a breather.
一息ついてるところ
I'm sorry though.
申し訳ないけど
What's going on?
どうなってるの?
I was a little shaky.
ちょっとガクガクした
Oh, it feels so good there.
あ、そこめっちゃ気持ちいい
Back, yeah.
背中、そうそう
Open your legs.
足を開いて
Oh no.
やば
Too cute.
かわいすぎる
Too cute
かわいすぎ
Ru.
る
Oh my goodness.
や ばいね
Please do.
どうぞね
amazing.
すごい
Super good.
超うまい
dangerous.
危ない
It's super good.
超うまいね
I have mixed feelings.
複雑な気持ち
a,
あ、
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Oh, no, I'll go.
あ、ダメ、行っちゃう
I went.
行っちゃった
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
I'm going.
行っちゃう
go.
行 く
行く
go.
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
Go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く
行 く、 行く、行く
difficult.
難しい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Stay behind.
後ろ手ついて
Sleep with your feet upright.
寝足立てて
It's moving slowly.
ゆっくり動いてて
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く
I'm going.
行っちゃう
Go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く
OK
行
Go, go, go.
く、 行く、行く
行 く、 行 く、行く
Ah, it feels so good
あー、すごい気持ちいい
!!
go go go go go go
いく 行く行く 行く行
Kume
く め
Well, the sound came back.
っちゃ 音返っちゃった
Ah, it feels good
あ ーーきもちいい
Ah... go
ああ...行く
go!
行 く!
行く!
go!
Feels good
気持ちいい
Feels good!
気 持ちいい!
気持ちいい!
Feels good!
Let's lean on each other's elbows, let's get up,
ちょっと肘つけてさ、起きあってさ、
Can you see where it is?
入っているところ見える?
Ah, it's embarrassing!
あー恥ずかしい!
appear!
見える!
It's full!
いっぱい入ってる!
feeling
気持ち
good!
いい!
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ず かしい?
It's embarrassing
恥ずかしいな
I'm starting to want to come. Is that okay?
来 たくなってきた いいの?
good?
いい?
go!
行く!
It's filled with so much! That's amazing!
いっぱい入っちゃったね すごい!